<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="shipping_and_returns">Shipping &amp; Returns</string>
    <string name="shopping_info_text">
        We have put a lot of focus on making sure the items get delivered to our customers as
        quickly as possible. You will receive your order in 6-17 business days from the date that it is placed.\n\n
        Verification\n
        A confirmation email will be sent to you once the order is authorized and verified. We begin
        preparing your order immediately after it is verified. With this sort of time frame, it makes
        it difficult for us to change or cancel your order, however, we will do our best to support your request.\n
        It normally takes 3-7 business days for us to process your order. Please note that this does not include holidays and weekends
    </string>
    <string name="return_info_text">
        Returns &amp; Exchanges\n
        If you\'re not 100% satisfied with the items you received, and we gladly accept returns within 30 days of
        receipt for most items in new condition.\n\n
        1. Get in touch with our customer service representative by sending us a ticket in your account. Indicate which item(s) you would
        like to return and the reason for your return.\n
        2. Place the item(s) in the original packing and seal the parcel securely.\n
        3. Drop off your package at the local post office.\n
        4. Most returns are processed within 5 business days after we receive your package. Once your refund has been issued, you will receive a confirmation email.\n\n
        Return Conditions\n
        1. You have 30 days to decide if an item is right for you if not, you can certainly come to us within 30 days of receipt.\n
        2. Items returned must be in their unused condition with the original packing. We do not accept a returned item that’s worn, damaged, washed or altered in any way.\n
        3. We do not accept returned items that were sent back to you directly without checking with us first.\n
        4. We do not offer Freight To Collect service for the packages returned to us. Shipping cost for the returned package is non-refundable.\n\n
        Return Address\n
        If you wish to return the items to the nearest return address, please submit a ticket in your account, our customer service representative will get back to you within 24 hours.\n\n\n
    </string>
</resources>